Name=ShuHulls
Author=Mr Shu, blacksun
Conflict=
Dependence=
Priority=5
Section=Shu's Rangers
SectionEng=Shu's Rangers
Languages=Rus,Eng

SmallDescription=Ребаланс серий корпусов
FullDescription=- Вдвое уменьшает шанс появления стандартных серий корпусов, значительно увеличивая распространенность всех прочих серий
FullDescription=- Увеличивает шанс появления редких серий корпусов
FullDescription=- Дорабатывает бонусы множества серий корпусов (очень многим сериям снижена восприимчивость для конкуренции с акриновыми корпусами, некоторым добавлены слоты артефактов, отдельным восприимчивость повышена)

SmallDescriptionEng=Rebalance hulls series
FullDescriptionEng=- Halves the chance of standard hulls series, greatly increasing the prevalence of all other series
FullDescriptionEng=- Increases the chance of rare series of hulls appearing
FullDescriptionEng=- Finalizes the bonuses of multiple hulls series (very many series have had their susceptibility reduced to compete with acrylic hulls, some have had artifact slots added, some have had their susceptibility increased)
