Name=ShuPrison
Author=Klaxons, Mr Shu
Conflict=
Dependence=UtilityFunctionsPack
Priority=5
Section=Shu's Rangers
SectionEng=Shu's Rangers
Languages=Rus,Eng

SmallDescription=Вносит вариативность в поведение NPC, оказавшихся в ней
FullDescription=Добавляет небольшой шанс гибели или совершение побега рейнджеров и пиратов в тюрьме, зависящий от расы планеты, на которой расположена тюрьма, а также от авторитета и здоровья пилота.

SmallDescriptionEng=Keeps the character's characteristics between restarts of the "Prison" quests and also introduces variability in the behavior of NPCs who was trapped in it
FullDescriptionEng=Keeps the "Strength" and "Intelligence" characteristics of the player character between restarts of the "Prison" quests, and allows you to take your prison pets with you. Also adds a small chance that rangers and pirates die or escape from prison. The chance depends on the race of the planets' inhabitors on which the prison is located, as well as the authority and health of the pilot.
