Name=BlockTextQ
Author=Klaxons, noname
Conflict=SR1TextQuests,RevTextQuests,ShuQuest,ShuQuestReward,RefQuest,AdvancedQuests
Dependence=
Priority=6
Section=Твики
SectionEng=Tweaks
Languages=Rus,Eng

SmallDescription=Отключает выдачу текстовых квестов в качестве правительственных заданий
FullDescription=Полностью отключает выдачу текстовых квестов в качестве правительственных заданий. Квест "Тюрьма", а также квесты, необходимые по пиратскому сюжету, отключены не будут.

SmallDescriptionEng=Disables the issuance of text quests as government missions
FullDescriptionEng=Completely disables the issuance of text quests as government missions. The Prison quest, as well as the quests necessary for the pirate plot, will not be disabled.