Name=EvoGkvan
Author=Mik,Владислав Зверинцев
Conflict=
Dependence=
Priority=2
Section=Universe
SectionEng=Universe
Languages=Rus,Eng

SmallDescription=Новый акриновый корпус "Гкван" с уникальным бонусом
FullDescription=Добавлен новый акриновый корпус (Гкван)
FullDescription=Корпус, воссозданный по чертежам неизвестной расы из другого рукава галактики - до недавнего времени засекреченный проект малоков. Разблокировка скоростного ограничителя осуществляется после подтверждении в биосканере того, что пилот является малоком.
FullDescription=Скорость: +200 ед. (только для малоков)

SmallDescriptionEng=New "Gkvan" acrylic hull with a unique perk
FullDescriptionEng=Added a new acrylic hull (Gkvan)
FullDescriptionEng=A hull recreated from the blueprints of an unknown race from another arm of the galaxy - until recently a classified Malogs project. The speed limiter is unlocked upon confirmation in the bioscanner that the pilot is a Malogs.
FullDescriptionEng=Speed: +200 units (Malogs only).
