Name=ShuWarriors
Author=Klaxons, Mr Shu
Conflict=
Dependence=ExpPilotBridge, UtilityFunctionsPack
Priority=5
Section=Shu's Rangers
SectionEng=Shu's Rangers
Languages=Rus,Eng

SmallDescription=Усиливает военных Коалиции и перерабатывает заказ военных операций на ВБ
FullDescription=<color=0,50,200>Нововведения мода:</color>
FullDescription=- Добавлен новый класс элитных военных, использующих акриновые корпуса и более мощное оборудование
FullDescription=- Полностью переработан заказ военных операций на военных базах
FullDescription=- Более высокое военное звание и максимальный навык лидерства игрока теперь будет открывать ему доступ к более гибкой настройке военной операции, начиная со звания "Ас" и выше (подробнее расскажут на военной базе)
FullDescription=- Поиск военных кораблей для заказной операции теперь происходит не в случайном приграничном секторе, а в том секторе, в котором находится сама военная база

SmallDescriptionEng=Strengthens the Coalition military and recycles the military operations order to the MB
FullDescriptionEng=<color=0,50,200>Mods innovations:</color>
FullDescriptionEng=- Added a new class of elite military using acrylic hulls and more powerful equipment
FullDescriptionEng=- Completely reworked the ordering of military operations on military bases
FullDescriptionEng=- A player's higher military rank and maximum leadership skill will now give them access to more flexible military operation customization, starting at the rank of "Ace" and higher (more details will be given at the military base)
FullDescriptionEng=- The search for warships for a commissioned operation no longer takes place in a random border sector, but in the sector in which the military base itself is located
